Hey , take it easy .
See you .
Turn it down .
- Ew , that geek ? - I 'm serious .
No way , I don 't care .
No way , you 're such a liar .
- I don 't know , he 's right behind us . - What ?
No way .
That one 's for you . He 's a live one .
Uh-uh , he 's yours . Oh , we 're coming to my house .
Hey , driver . Hey !
Hey , driver , that was my stop .
Driver , that was my stop .
Driver , what 's going on ?
Where are we going ?
Let us out . Come on .
- Driver ? - What are you doing ?
Stop it !
Stop !
Please . Please stop .
- What 's happening ? - I don 't know .
Oh , my God .
What 's going on ?
Oh , my God . We 're stuck here .
Oh , my God ! What is this ?
What 's that ?
- What is it ? - Oh , my God , it 's him ! Come on !
Oh , my God !
Open this thing . He 's coming !
- No ! - God !
- Oh , my God , come on ! - Save us !
Get the door .
Mommy , why can 't Jesse wake up like everybody else ?
Oh , honey , he 's all right .
He 's just having a bad dream .
Mm . Thank you .
Good morning , honey .
Hi , Ma .
Well , two more . Hallelujah .
I want that room unpacked by tonight , young man .
Okay , Dad . I promise .
I don 't want any more promises , Jesse .
- I want that room cleaned up , okay ? - All right , I 'll get on it .
No .
- Angie , what are you up to ? - I 'm trying to get the Fuman fingers .
- Want some eggs ? - No .
Jesse , are you okay ?
It 's so hot up there , I 'm having trouble sleeping .
I know . Ken , I wish you 'd call somebody and have the air conditioning - -
There 's absolutely nothing wrong with that air conditioning , Mom .
Just needs a shot of Freon .
- Here they are . - Oh , no .
Come on , Dad , you 're not trying to fix something again .
Nobody likes a smart ass , buddy boy .
Look .
Who 's that ?
It 's Lisa .
I gotta get to school .
Whoa , whoa . Who 's Lisa ?
Who is Lisa ?
Just eat your eggs , dear .
- Hi . - Hi .
Don 't you ever use a key ?
Why ?
Somebody could steal your car , couldn 't they ?
The deadly dinosaur ?
Strike .
Grady , come on , you can hit this stuff .
You ready , girls ?
That was very good .
Easy out .
Easy hit . Easy hit .
- Ha ! - Strike .
Get him out of there already .
Didn 't feel right , okay ? Give me a break .
So you getting any yet , Lise ?
Kerry , he 's my ride to school , okay ?
Put it out . Put it out .
- You all right ? - Yeah .
- You okay there ? - Yeah .
Good shot , good shot .
You Okay ?
Yeah , I 'm fine .
Well , pay attention next time .
Very heads-up play .
Nice catch , Walsh .
Come on , come on . Let 's go .
Come on , Mitch .
All right !
Come on .
Knock him down .
You 're out .
Heads up play , Grad ) ' -
All right ! All right !
Nice ass .
Come on ! Get him !
Come on , slug him !
Go on , slug him !
Slug him . Come on , slug him !
Slug him !
- Here comes Schneider . - Watch out .
- You can get him , come on ! - Get out of my way .
- Come on . - Okay , dirtballs .
Come on .
Assume the position .
See you around , coach .
Hey , man , chill out , dude .
Shut up , dude .
Come on . Come on .
How much longer do you think he 's gonna keep us out here ?
It could be all night .
The guy gets his rocks off like this .
Hangs around queer SM joints downtown .
He likes pretty boys like you .
Get out of here .
What about you and that babe you 've been cruising to school with every day ?
What about her ?
Are you mounting her nightly or what ?
Look , Grady , you got some problem with me ?
No , bro .
Just killing time .
Oh , God , that 's gross .
Okay , dirtballs , hit the shower .
So you live around here or what ?
Yeah , my parents just bought a place on Elm Street .
Elm Street ?
You moved into that big white house with bars in the window ?
Yeah , what about it ?
Shit . You can tell your old man he 's a real chump .
What are you talking about now , Grady ?
Some chick was locked in there by her mother and she went crazy .
She watched her boyfriend get butchered across the street by some maniac .
You 're full of shit , Grady .
Dad ?
Dad !
Help !
Daddy can 't help you now .
Shh .
I need you , Jesse .
We 've got special work to do here , you and me .
You 've got the body
I 've got the brain .
Jess ?
Jesse .
- Do you think we should call the doctor ? - No .
No , I 'm fine .
It 's just a bad dream , okay ?
Yeah .
Yeah , go to sleep .
So to review .
The solid wastes , those nutrients not absorbed in the lining of the stomach
the large intestine , the small intestine
and the elementary canal are passed out through the colon .
Liquid nutrients are then carried through an elaborate system of filtering
aided by the pancreas , liver and gall bladder
or collected in the bladder to be expelled at a later time .
And this entire process is kept moving
through the circulatory system , the center of which is
the heart .
- Yeah ! - Ew .
Four chambers .
Just like the human heart , really .
From the body to the right auricle , to the right ventricle
and out the pulmonary arteries to the lungs .
There it trades off carbon dioxide for oxygen .
Carbon dioxide is exhaled and the oxygenated blood continues to ...
Into the left auricle through the left ventricle passing out of the ...
No !
If you wanna play with animals , Mr. Walsh , join the circus .
Lisa , sweetheart , there 's a Jesse on the phone .
Okay . Thanks , Mom .
Jesse ?
Hi .
On the national front ...
- Where are you going , Jess ? - Just out for a little while .
I told you I want that room unpacked .
- I 'm just going out for an hour or two . - No .
Upstairs .
Right now , son .
Right now .
Ooh , you know how to love me , yeah
When we make love tonight
How do you like that , Dad ?
I need you so bad , baby
Oh , oh
This is where you belong
Don 't make me wait too long
No
All night long
Hold me , baby Drive me crazy
Touch me all night long
Make me love you Kiss and hug you
Jesse .
Touch me all night long
You 're my candy man
Ha . I 'll , uh - - I 'll leave the two of you alone .
Excuse me .
I told her you invited me over .
I guess maybe I should have called .
No . Ha , ha . It 's fine , really .
I mean , I was just cleaning my room .
I know .
I figured you might like some help .
Where does this go ?
Um ... Do your sweaters go in the closet ?
What 's this ?
I don 't know . Looks like a diary to me .
Let 's see .
" Nancy Thompson . 1428 Elm Street . "
That 's right here .
Hey , you know , this thing is five years old .
- You know her ? - Uh-uh . No . Before my time .
Wait , listen to this .
" Sometimes when I 'm lying here in bed
I can see Glen in his window across the way getting ready for bed .
His body is slim and smooth
and I know I shouldn 't watch him but that part of me that wants him
forces me to .
That 's when I weaken .
That 's when I wanna go to him . "
- Can I see that ? - Mm-hm .
" March 15th .
He comes to me at night .
Horrible , ugly , dirty , under the sheets with me .
Tearing at my nightgown with his steel claws .
His name is Fred
and he keeps trying to take me to the boiler room .
He wants to kill me . "
What is it ?
" Tina is dead . "
Jesse , are you okay ?
It 's just something that Grady said to me .
About the girl that used to live here ?
How she went crazy when she saw her boyfriend get murdered across the street .
Ugh .
Go ahead , Jesse .
Try it on for size .
Kill for me .
It was kind of like I was sleepwalking .
Maybe you were having a premonition or something , you know .
Like the guys who help police solve crimes and find missing people .
Ever have anything like this happen before ?
Nope . Never .
- You think that 's what it is ? - I don 't know .
Can I see the diary for a little while ?
Thanks .
- Hi , guys . - Hi , Kerry .
I got your invitation for the party this weekend .
Any cute guys gonna be there ?
All of them . Ha , ha .
Is your dad gonna be the DJ again ?
- Mom is gonna keep him upstairs this time . - Oh , good .
Uh , ha , ha .
Last party I had
my Dad insisted on playing Benny Goodman records all night .
- Well , I 'll see you later , okay ? - Okay .
Hey , Grady , do you remember your dreams ?
Only the wet ones .
No talking .
Hey , Grady .
You know , Schneider shouldn 't have called you out on that last play .
Yeah , well , Schneider has got a stick up his ass today .
Schneider 's always got a stick up his ass .
Hello , dirtballs .
- Ugh . It is so hot in here . - Yeah , babe .
Let me look at the thermostat .
My God , it is hot as an oven in here .
Shh . The birds are sleeping .
Cheryl , it 's 97 degrees in here .
Damn it . Ow !
Angela , watch out .
Watch out , Jesse .
- Ah ! - Ken , are you all right ?
Cheryl - - Damn bird . Look out , Angela , get out .
Look out , Jesse .
- Come on . - Look out , Angela .
Jesse , get out of here .
Cheryl .
What are you doing , Jesse ? Help me move this thing .
- It isn 't the gas . - Don 't tell me it 's not the gas .
Your mother thought she smelled gas .
- Well , I thought I did , I wasn 't sure . - All right , so , what is it , bird rabies ?
- It 's that seed you 've been buying . - Please , Ken , really .
No , it could be . Got to be a rational explanation .
Animals don 't explode into flames for no reason , do they ?
- That 's right . - All right .
Well , it 's sure not a leaky gas pipe .
- You all right ? - Oh , it 's all right .
You set this whole thing up , didn 't you ?
What are you talking about ?
You know what I 'm talking about . What did you use , firecrackers ?
You know what he did , he used a goddamn cherry bomb .
- Stop it . - That 's what he did .
Look , you can 't talk to me like that .
- Jesse , come back . Jesse . - Ken .
- Come back , Jesse ! - Stop it , you 're being ridiculous .
- Now come on , stop it . - Jesse !
Shit .
Oh , jeez .
- I don 't know , he always wants to - - - Don 't touch me .
Can I have a beer , please ?
Hit the shower .
No , no , no ! No !
No , no !
No , goddamn it , no !
No !
No , no .
Oh , boy .
Good evening , uh , does this belong to you ?
Uh , yes , sir , he 's my son .
We found him out on the highway wandering around .
He was naked .
I 'd keep a short leash on him if I were you .
Thank you , officer .
Jesse , come here , come .
Hey , hey .
Come here .
Two questions .
You answer them and we can all go to bed , all right ?
What are you taking , son ?
Who are you getting it from ?
I 'm not taking drugs .
- Mom , I wanna go to bed . - Yeah , come on .
It 's just a problem I have to work out on my own .
- But something 's bothering you . - Mom .
We 're just concerned about you - - Jesse .
- I 'm fine , just leave me alone . - Can 't - - ?
- Can 't we at least talk about it ? - No .
He needs professional help . I think we have to take him to a psychiatrist .
Come on , Cheryl , you 're out of your gourd . What will that do ?
I don 't know . He needs help and we don 't know how to give it .
- Oh , come on , Cheryl . - Are you hearing me ?
- That boy 's in trouble . - No , he 's not in trouble .
What that boy needs is a good goddamn kick in the butt .
That 's what he needs .
I 'll tell you what he needs . He needs a methadone clinic .
What 's happening ?
I want all you students back to your classes ...
Don 't worry about what ...
Just don 't worry about it . Let them do their work , all right ?
Yo , man , where have you been ?
- Schneider got wasted last night . - Oh , my God .
He must have been working late . Some maniac sliced him like a kielbasa .
Hacked him in the shower . Got bloody footprints all over the place .
Stand back from the line , please .
Kill for me .
One , two
Freddy 's coming for you
Three , four
Better lock your door
Five , six
Grab your crucifix
- Morning , Jess . - Morning .
Dad , how come it took them five years to sell this house ?
Oh , I don 't know .
They just couldn 't get the right price , I suppose .
Didn 't know about the murder across the street ?
The girl that lived here that saw the whole thing .
They told me something about it , yeah , but I - -
- You knew something about this - - - Come on , Cheryl .
How do you think we got such a good deal here , hon ?
Did they tell you that that girl lost her mind ?
And her mother killed herself in our living room ?
- What ? - Did they tell you that ?
Mom , I 'm scared .
- Come here . - Oh , honey , it 's all right .
Daddy and Jesse are just pretending , that 's all .
I don 't think this is something we should discuss .
See ? Don 't wanna hear one more word about it .
There 's absolutely nothing , I mean nothing , wrong with this house .
Come on .
Is something burning ?
Good Lord .
It 's the craziest damn thing I 've ever seen .
Look here , Cheryl .
It wasn 't even plugged in .
Jesse , you can 't blame yourself for what happened to Schneider .
And just because you dreamt it doesn 't mean you did it .
- Where are we going ? - Veer leftover here .
Look , I really think this is all in your mind , you know
like you 're picking up some psychic signals .
Wow , what is this place ?
Do you remember in the diary ?
When Nancy said she kept finding herself in a boiler room ?
Well , Fred Krueger worked here . It 's an old power plant .
- Here . - What is all this ?
I did some reading on our friend , Fred Krueger .
- How long has it been closed down ? - A long time .
Come on .
Jesus .
Fred Krueger kidnapped 20 kids
and brought them here and killed them .
- Do you feel anything ? - What do you mean ?
I don 't know . I thought you might be able to make a connection or something .
- I feel like a jerk . - Shh . Just concentrate .
Do you feel anything ?
Uh-uh .
Wake up , little girl .
What time is it ?
It 's late , go back to sleep .
Morning , honey . Did you sleep okay ?
Yeah , fine .
Good . You 're looking better .
You had another nightmare , didn 't you ?
Yes , I had a bad night .
Do you wanna talk about it ?
My dad thinks I 'm on drugs .
My mom thinks I 'm crazy .
And you know , at this point , I don 't know if I don 't agree with her .
Hey , what 's wrong with Jesse ? He seems kind of freaked out .
Hey , wanna go to a movie or something , hang out ?
Maybe get these things off your mind . Get a pizza or something .
Hey , guys .
Hi , Ronnie .
- You going to Lisa 's house tomorrow night ? - No .
- I can 't , I 'm grounded . - How come ?
I threw my grandmother down a flight of stairs .
Jesse .
Jesse , I think you should eat something .
- I 'm not hungry . - I wish you would talk to me .
You know , we can figure it out . We can figure it out together .
There is nothing to figure out .
I don 't know why you 're wasting your time .
- He 's a basket case . - Shut up , Grady .
Want me to shut up ? Fine , I 'll shut up , no problem .
See you around , buddy .
Here you are .
- Hey . - All right .
Hey , now cut that out .
I 've got it .
But , sweetheart , it 's a nice party .
Come on , Skinny , it 's time for bed .
You 're in charge , hotshot .
Twelve-thirty , miss , no later .
- Twelve-thirty . - Have a nice time .
Hi .
What 's the matter with Jesse ?
I don 't know .
- Jesse ? - I 'll be out in a second .
Can I please come in and talk to you ?
Listen , I 'm gonna leave . I 'm not into this .
I 'm sorry .
Jesse , why won 't you talk to me ?
- Will you just leave me alone ? - You 're not being fair .
I wanna help you .
How can you help me ?
What are you gonna do for me ?
Look , I feel like I 'm losing my mind .
And I don 't want you to watch me fall apart .
I 'm afraid to go to sleep .
I 'm afraid to stay awake .
I 'm ruining your party .
- They 're gonna take me away . - Come on , don 't say that .
Listen , we 'll stay up all night if we have to .
I 'm not gonna let anything happen to you .
Come on , any second now , any second .
Yeah , party time .
I got the music .
I wanna tell you Exactly how I feel
- What the hell are they doing down there ? - Oh , Eddie , they 're kids .
I know they 're kids . I gotta get some rest .
Now that you 're leaving It 's time that I confess
The way we planned our love together
Sometimes doing more is less
From a whisper to a scream Now I know just what it means
From a whisper to a scream I said I love you
Yesterday you were only mine Today you 're loving somebody new
What is it ?
Jesse , what 's wrong ?
Jesus Christ , you scared the shit out of me , man .
Hey , what are you doing ?
Hey , what the fuck are you doing in my room ?
Listen , I 'm in trouble .
I need you to let me stay here tonight .
Are you out of your mind ?
I don 't know .
Oh , man .
Why don 't you just go home and take a bottle of sleeping pills ?
I killed Schneider .
You what ?
Only it wasn 't me , see ?
There 's something inside of me .
And last night it made me go to my sister 's room .
And tonight with Lisa in the cabana it started to happen again .
I think you are seriously losing it , bro .
I 'm scared , Grady .
Something is trying to get inside my body .
Yeah , she 's female , she 's waiting for you in the cabana .
And you wanna sleep with me .
Look , I don 't care if you believe me or not .
Hey , I believe you .
You 've had some scary dreams , okay ?
No .
I don 't know .
I 'm all messed up .
What difference does it make ?
I 'm in trouble . And I need you to help me .
Okay ?
All right , man . What do you want me to do ?
Just watch me .
And if anything starts to happen
if I start to act weird , start dreaming weird
or try to walk out of here , you gotta stop me .
I don 't care if you have to hit me over the head , just don 't let me leave .
And , Grady
don 't fall asleep .
Hot dog ?
Come back in the water .
I 'm busy , okay ?
I don 't know , Kerry . I feel like I should go see him .
But I can 't just leave the party .
Fuck the party .
Go see him .
Yeah .
Leaving the land of the dead , and with Torch - -
I want you to meet Louie - -
And now I see the - -
See , kid , you 're a dog .
You sure handled that situation - -
Throw me a line . That changes into a bottomless pit !
Sweet dreams , pal .
- Grady . - What ?
It 's starting to happen again .
Jesus .
Hey , man .
What the fuck 's wrong with you , dude ?
Shit .
Oh , my God .
Dad !
Dad , open the door !
No !
Dad ! Dad !
Dad !
Oh , my God !
Dad , open the door ! Dad !
Dad !
Ron .
Ron , what is it ?
Dad !
Ron , open the door !
Ron , are you all right ?
Ron , this is your father , open this door !
No ! No !
" No ! " Ron !
RON , open it up ! Ron !
Get help !
No .
You son of a bitch !
You killed him !
No !
Somebody in there ? Open up .
It 's locked . Break it down .
Take a rose
Call it sorrow
But it 's a rose by any other name
Jesse , my God , what happened ?
I killed him . I killed him .
Jesse , my God , you 're hurt . What happened ?
I - - I killed Grady .
I killed Grady .
Lisa , I killed Schneider .
Oh , no , my God .
I 'm so scared .
Jesse , what are you talking about ?
He 's inside me .
- I 'm scared . - Jesse , who is doing this to you ?
Fred Krueger .
He 's inside me , and he wants to take me again .
No . No .
Jesse .
Jesse , this is not happening .
It 's got to be everything you 've taken in . Uh , Schneider , the diary , the glove .
Only it 's all mixed up - -
Christ , what do I have to do to make you understand me ?
Last night he made me try to kill my sister .
I 've got blood on my hands .
He owns me .
Hey , could somebody turn down the heat in the pool ?
What 's going on ?
Shit .
- Hey , Rocky . - Our hero .
Jesse .
Come on , I just want you to listen to this .
It 's something Nancy said in the last page of her diary .
Listen .
" He is evil itself .
I know now that I brought him into my world .
We all did .
Gave him all the energy he needed .
Our screams were all he needed . "
Lisa ?
Jesse , she wasn 't crazy . All this really happened .
You can fight him .
Oh , God , he 's coming back .
- Get out of here , Lisa . - Jesse , fight him .
I can 't .
Fight it , Jesse .
You created him , you can destroy him .
Lisa , open this door .
He is living off of your fear .
- Jesse , fight him . - I can 't !
Yes , you can .
Fight him .
You are not afraid of him .
- He doesn 't even exist . - No !
Oh , my God .
Jesse ?
He can 't fight me . I 'm here .
No , no !
Help !
No !
Jesse !
Help !
Oh , my God !
No !
Don 't .
- It 's gotten a little hot . - What 's going on in there ?
My God !
Jesse , help .
There is no Jesse .
I 'm Jesse now .
Get away from me !
Kill me , Lisa .
Please , kill me .
Come on , Lisa , kill him .
Kill him .
I love you , Lisa .
No .
Oh , God .
Help , please .
Please .
No .
I love you , Lisa .
Jesse , help .
Hey , is everybody okay ?
Search me .
What 's going on ?
Wait a minute ! Wait !
Ah ! It 's hot .
Lisa . Lisa .
Lisa . Oh , my God , are you all right ?
Mommy .
Get her out of here !
- Get out of here ! - All right .
Hey .
Just calm down , all right ?
Relax .
Yeah . It 's gonna be all right .
Nobody 's gonna hurt you .
Just tell us what you want , all right ?
Okay , I 'm here to help you .
Help yourself , fucker .
You are all my children now .
Oh , shit .
No ! Don 't .
What the hell are you doing ?
Where did he go ?
Come to me , Lisa .
Jesse , I know you 're in there .
- Stop him . - No , no , no , Jesse 's dead .
Jesse .
Lisa .
I love you , Jesse .
Come back to me , Lisa .
I am not afraid of you .
He 's in there and I want him back .
I 'm gonna take him away from you .
And you are gonna go straight back to hell , you son of a bitch !
No , Jesse 's dead .
Come back to me , Jesse .
I love you .
Come back to me .
He 's dead .
He can 't hold you , Jesse .
He 's losing his grip .
You can get out .
He 'll die with me .
He 'll die with both of us .
Lisa ! Lisa !
Jesse .
It 's great to have you home again , Jess .
I can 't believe I 'm going back . I 'm glad .
- Good . - I 'm glad .
- Have a good day , huh ? - Okay .
Thanks , Mom .
Bye .
Hi .
Hi , Jesse .
What is so funny ?
That was a really great party .
- Thanks , Lise . - Thanks a lot .
I can 't believe it 's actually all over .
- Let 's not talk about it . - Okay .
Ooh . Ha , ha . - ls this - - ?
Am I going crazy or is this bus going too fast ?
It 's going fine .
No problem .
No .
This bus is going too fast .
- Lisa , it 's starting to speed up . - It 's fine .
It 's fine .
Driver .
- Driver , stop . - Jesse , just sit down .
I 'm sorry .
It 's okay . It 's all right .
Jesse , it 's okay .
It 's all over .